Hello. My name is Dana Shin,
大家好 我叫 Dana Shin
and I'll be your instructor for spreadsheets.
我将是你的电子表格讲师
I'm an Engineer and Computer Scientist.
我是一名工程师和计算机科学家
I've been using spreadsheets since early in my career when they first came out.
从早期电子表格刚出现起 我就开始使用它了
In this introduction to spreadsheets,
在这门电子表格入门课程中
we'll focus on how to leverage some of the powerful features that
我们将重点讲解如何利用电子表格的一些强大功能
makes spreadsheets a must for your data analysis tool box.
使其成为必备数据分析工具
Here's how the lessons are organized.
下面介绍下课程结构
In this first lesson,
在第一节课
I'll give you a little background and then you'll jump right in.
我将介绍一些背景知识 然后开始使用电子表格
We'll set up a spreadsheet,
我们将创建一个电子表格
go over some major features,
介绍一些重要功能
without going into too much depth,
但是不会深入讲解
just to get you started.
只讲解入门知识
If you're already familiar with the basics of spreadsheets,
如果你已经熟悉电子表格的基础知识
it's okay to skip ahead to the exercises and quizzes.
可以直接跳到练习和测验部分
After getting started, we'll focus on how to manipulate data,
开始后 我们将重点讲解如何处理数据
analyze data and finally, visualize data.
分析数据 最终可视化数据
Along the way, I'll show you lots of examples,
在这一过程中 我将展示大量的示例
and you'll have the opportunity to try out what you've
你可以利用在简短练习和测验中学到的知识
learned in small exercises and quizzes.
尝试求解这些示例
That is, I'll demonstrate a concept or group of features,
我将演示一个概念或一组功能
then you'll be given some small challenges in the form of quizzes or exercises.
然后以测验或练习的形式提出一些挑战题目
These are designed to reinforce what you see in the videos,
这些挑战旨在巩固你在视频中学到的知识
so be sure to give them a try.
因此务必尝试求解
Also, keep an eye out for key terms and
此外 请留意讲师注释中的关键术语
special pro tips in the instructor notes on the shortcuts and time-savers.
和特殊专业提示 帮助你找到捷径并节省时间
Now, you may be wondering which spreadsheet you're going to learn about.
你可能会疑问 你将学习哪种电子表格
The answer is, any of them.
答案是任何电子表格都行
I'll be demonstrating with Excel on Windows but,
我将演示 Windows 上的 Excel
you're welcome to use any spreadsheet you have ready
但是当你求解测验和练习题时
access to when you're trying the quizzes and exercises.
可以使用任何你能够使用的电子表格
There are a number of different spreadsheet applications out there to choose from,
有很多不同的电子表格应用可以选择
Microsoft Excel is the most popular and is robust and mature.
Microsoft Excel 是最流行也最稳定强大的电子表格
Google sheets won't do everything that Excel can,
Excel 中的某些功能 Google 表格并不具备
but it's free and collaborative.
但是 Google 表格是免费的 可以协作使用
Then, there's Apple numbers and Apache Open Office Calc and more.
还有 Apple Numbers 和 Apache Open Office Calc 等
The interfaces and some of the details differ between
不同电子表格应用以及计算机平台之间的
spreadsheet applications as well as between computer platforms,
界面和某些细节部分会有所不同
but they share a number of core features and functions.
但是它们都具备一些核心功能
Your exercises and quizzes in the lessons will use a format that all of these support.
这节课中的练习和测验将使用所有应用和平台都支持的格式